Narrator: 1
Eve: Do you like the book?
Wendy: Yes, I do. It’s very good.
Eve: She’s my favourite writer.
I love her books.
Narrator: 2
Eve: Do you live in New York?
Wendy: No, I don’t. I live in London.
My husband and I work for a British company.
Eve: Oh!
Do you have children?
Wendy: No, we don’t.
Eve: I have two sons and a daughter.
David and Andrew are at university and Carla’s at school.
Look. Here are some photos…
This is a photo of our holiday in Barbados.
Do you know Barbados?
Wendy: No, I don’t.
Narrator: 3
Attendant: Do you want meat, fish, or pasta?
Eve: Oh, fish, please.
Wendy: Pasta for me, please.
Eve: How’s your pasta?
Wendy: It’s OK.
Eve: This fish isn’t very good.
Excuse me, I don’t like this fish.
Can I have the pasta, please?
Attendant: I’m sorry, madam. It’s finished.
Narrator: 4
Eve: Oh, I need to go to the toilet.
Oops, sorry.
Wendy: Excuse me. What time do we arrive?
Attendant: In twenty-five minutes, madam.
Wendy: That’s good!